mobileworldlive.com 2014-11-21

# Privacy Policy | Mobile World LiveMobile World Live

### Introduction

The GSM Association and its group companies, including but not limited to GSMC Limited (hereinafter referred to as “GSMA”), take the privacy of your information very seriously. This website privacy policy (“Policy”) explains how and for what purposes we use the information collected about you through the mobileworldlive.com (referred to below as the “Site”). Please read this Policy carefully.

By using the Site and any services we offer via the Site, you are agreeing to be bound by this Policy in respect of the information collected about you via this Site. You acknowledge and agree (on your own behalf and duly authorised on behalf of any third party whose details you supply) that the processing (including disclosure) of personal information is necessary or desirable for the provision of relevant services and the operation of GSMAâs performance of its rights and obligations owed to you or a third party.

The references to information ‘relating to you’ or ‘about you’ include references to information about your employees, representatives, agents, directors, officers, shareholders or other relevant parties whose details you have provided and those of your affiliates and subsidiaries and sub-contractors and those of any third party whose details you supply to GSMA.

We may update this Policy from time to time to take account of changing requirements and we request that you refer back to this Policy frequently to review any revisions. If at any time we decide to use personal information in a manner significantly different to that stated in this Policy, or otherwise disclosed to you at the time it was collected, we will notify you by email, and you will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this new manner. If you have any queries about the Policy, please get in touch with us using the contact details set out at Contact Us below and we will do our best to answer your questions.

### Collection & Use of Information

We do not collect personal information about you on this Site apart from information for which you volunteer, for example by completing the online registration form or using the “Contact Us” function. The information collected may include the following:  
\- your name, company name, title in your Company;  
\- your email address, postal address, telephone and fax numbers;  
\- credit card information and bank details if provided.

We will use your contact details in order to respond to any queries submitted by you.

We may also use your information:  
\- to provide you with information, including marketing information in relation to upcoming GSM Association or industry events, meetings, conferences, seminars, offers, products or services which we believe could be of interest to you or your organisation;  
\- to carry out surveys and to get your views in relation to the products or services which we or third parties provide;  
\- to invite individuals to be speakers at seminars/training events, or to participate in other meetings or events held by us or third parties.

We may contact you by any means of communication for which you have given us contact details, including email, telephone and post. However, you may choose not to receive such information by so indicating on the online registration form at the time of providing your information or by simply using the ‘Contact Us’ function below.  
Any financial details supplied to us such as bank details and/or credit card details are used solely for the purpose of processing payments.

### Sharing of information

Your data may be passed to third party companies who provide training courses, mailing services and event management on behalf of GSMA. In addition, we may pass your information to our related companies [The GSM Association and its affiliated companies], carefully selected business partners or other carefully selected third parties who may contact you to provide you with information, including marketing information in relation to upcoming industry events, meetings, conferences, seminars, offers, products or services which could be of interest to you or your business and/or to carry out surveys and to get your views in relation to the products or services which third parties provide. If you do not wish us to provide your information to third parties for these purposes, please indicate that to us at the time of providing your information by contacting us at [database@gsma.com](mailto:database@gsma.com). On occasion, we may use third party agents and service providers to assist us in the use of your data as outlined above.

We may provide your personal information to a third party as part of a sale or transfer of some or all of our business and assets to any third party or as part of any business restructuring or reorganisation, but we will take steps with the aim of ensuring that your privacy rights continue to be protected.

Other than as set out above, we will not disclose any of your personal information without your permission unless we are required by law to do so (for example, if required to do so by a court order or for the prevention of fraud or other crime).

Transferring your information outside of the European Economic Area (“EEA”)  
In using your information as set out in this Policy, it may be transferred to countries outside the EEA. By way of example, this may happen if one of our service providers is located in a country outside the EEA. We also may share your information with our associated companies, business partners or other carefully selected third parties which are located in countries worldwide. These countries may not have similar data protection laws to the EEA. If we transfer your information outside of the EEA in this way, we will take steps aiming to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected.

### Information automatically collected from your computer

When you visit the Site, our web server automatically records your IP address. This IP address may be linked to any of your personal information. We use IP addresses to help us administer the Site and to collect demographic information for marketing and aggregation purposes.

We may also gather other non-personal information (from which we cannot identify you) such as the type of your Internet browser, which we use to provide you with a more effective service.

### Cookies

When you visit the Site we may store some information (commonly known as a “cookie”) on your computer. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your hard drive to store and sometimes track information about you. In this regard, please review our cookie policy at which sets out the purposes for which we use cookies and how they can be disabled.

### Changes to your details

We aim to keep our information about you as accurate as possible. If you would like to review or change the details that we hold about you, please contact us at database@gsm.org  
Security

We are committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We have implemented appropriate technology and policies to safeguard your personal information from unauthorised access and improper use. However, the nature of the Internet is such that we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us via the Internet.  
Linking to third party websites

We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other sites, even if you access them using links from this Site. We strongly recommend that you check the policy of each site you visit and contact its owner or operator if you have any concerns or questions.

In addition, if you linked to this Site from a third party site, we are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of the owners or operators of that third party site. We strongly recommend that you check the policy of that third party site and contact its owner or operator if you have any concerns or questions.

### Contact us

If at any time you would like to contact us with your views about our privacy practices, or with any enquiry relating to your personal information, or if you do not wish us to continue using your information as outlined above, you can do so by sending an email to us at [database@gsma.com](mailto:database@gsma.com) or write to CRM Manager, GSMC Limited, 1000 Abernathy Road, Suite 450 Atlanta, Georgia 30328 USA.
